Guide to the Seattle Design Commission Project Files 1968-1986
Seattle Municipal Archives
Seattle Design Commission Project Files
1968-1986
City of Seattle Seattle Municipal Archives PO Box 94728 600 Fourth Avenue, Floor 3 Seattle, WA 98124-4728 Phone: 206/233-7807 Email: archives@seattle.gov http://www.seattle.gov/cityarchives
9323-02
Seattle Design Commission
8.6 cubic feet 21 boxes
Records detailing projects reviewed by the Design Commission.
Historical Note
The Seattle Design Commission (SDC) was established in 1968 to ensure that public facilities and projects incorporate high standards of design quality. The SDC reviews public projects and makes recommendations in the areas of urban design context, public access, open space planning, integration of public art, and streetscape design. SDC review is a required element of the public design review process. The Commission is comprised of ten citizens, including artists, architects, urban planners, engineers, environmental planners, and landscape architects. Commissioners are appointed to two-year terms by the Mayor and are confirmed by City Council.
Correspondence, excerpts from minutes, proposals, maps, plans, photographs, memoranda, clippings, reports, and other material relating to projects of the Design Commission. Contains files for projects begun from 1968 through 1977, including the Seattle Aquarium, Woodland Park Zoo expansions, and Pike Place Market rehabilitations and improvements.
Records are open to the public.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Seattle Design Commission
Seattle (Wash.)
Seattle Aquarium; Pike Place Market (Seattle, Wash.); Woodland Park Zoo; City planning--Washington (State)--Seattle
Seattle; City Planning
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Seattle Design Commission Project Files, 1968-1986; 9323-02
  - Seattle-First National Bank - Street Lights 10/31/68.1, 1968 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - 23rd Avenue and Rainier Avenue - Street Widening 10/31/68.2, 1968 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Fire Station 27 Design 10/31/68.3, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Sick's Stadium Remodeling 10/31/68.4, 1968 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Garfield Swimming Pool / Medgar Evers Memorial Pool 10/31/68.5, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Jackson Golf Course Concession Building 10/31/68.6, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Camp Long Parking Lot 10/31/68.7, 1968 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Laurelhurst Recreation Center Parking Lot 10/31/68.8, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Sign Bridges and Cantilevered Signs 10/31/68.9, 1968 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Fremont Bridge Railings 10/31/68.10, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - R. H. Thomson Freeway Briefing 10/31/68.11, 1968 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - South Seattle Urban Renewal Project 10/31/68.12, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Food Circus Renovation 11/14/68.1, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - North and South Leschi Moorages 11/14/68.2, 1968-1979 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Nocturnal House and Small Mammal Grottoes 11/14/68.3, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Transit Passenger Shelters 11/14/68.5, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Leschi Playground 11/14/68.8, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Miller Playfield 11/14/68.9, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Wallingford Playfield 11/14/68.10, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - South Spokane Street Improvement 11/14/68.12, 1968 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - South Lander Street Improvement 11/14/68.13, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Northeast 125th Street Improvement 11/14/68.14, 1968 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Fire Station 25 12/12/68.1, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Delridge Substation 12/12/68.2, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - East Pine Street Pumping Station 12/12/68.3, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Water Department Shops 12/12/68.4, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - 15th Avenue Northwest Widening 12/12/68.5, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - Spruce Park (Mini-Park) 12/12/68.6, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - Fire House Park (Mini-Park) 12/12/68.7, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - Jackson Park (Mini-Park) 12/12/68.8, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - West Queen Anne Playfield 12/12/68.9, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (Lake Union) 12/12/68.10, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - Matthews Beach Park Launching Ramp 12/12/68.11, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Hughes and View Ridge Playground Wading Pool 12/12/68.12, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/34)
  - View Ridge Playfield Wading Pool 12/12/68.13, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/35)
  - Rainier Playfield Athletic Field Lighting 12/12/68.14, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 1/36)
  - Madrona Playground Lighting 12/12/68.15, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/37)
  - Park Department Administration Building Remodeling 12/12/68.16, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/38)
  - Magnolia Viewpoint 12/12/68.17, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 1/39)
  - Kerry Park Sculpture 12/12/68.18, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 1/40)
  - Bookmobile Station and Charles Street Shops 1/9/69.2, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/41)
  - West Seattle Freeway 1/9/69.3, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 1/42)
  - West Seattle Freeway 1/9/69.3, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 1/43)
  - West Seattle Freeway 1/9/69.3, 1973 (Box-folder 1/44)
  - West Seattle Freeway 1/9/69.3, 1972 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - West Seattle Freeway 1/9/69.3, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - West Seattle Freeway 1/9/69.3 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - North Greenwood Playground 1/9/69.6, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Pinehurst Playground Shelter House 1/9/69.7, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Montlake Playfield 1/9/69.8, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Jefferson Park Recreation Center 1/9/69.9, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Sick's Stadium Parking 1/17/69.2, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Miscellaneous Street Projects 2/13/69.5-2/13/69.13, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - West Marginal Way Southwest 2/13/69.14, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Safeco Pedestrian Overpass 2/27/69.2, 1969 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - 12th Avenue Northeast Widening 2/27/69.3, 1969 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Zoo Master Plan 2/13/69.16, 1969-1982 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Zoo Master Plan 2/13/69.16, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Zoo Master Plan 2/13/69.16, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - Zoo Master Plan 2/13/69.16, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - Fire Station 11 2/27/69.5, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - Lincoln Park 2/27/69.6, 1969 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - East Queen Anne Playground 2/27/69.10, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Rainier Playfield 2/27/69.11, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 2/20)
  - Alleys in Berkshire Addition 3/13/69.7, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/21)
  - Alleys in Block 2, Brygger's Addition 3/13/69.8, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/22)
  - 38th Avenue Northeast - Sidewalks 3/13/69.9, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/23)
  - Fire Station 23 3/27/69.1, 1969 (Box-folder 2/24)
  - Jefferson Park Lawn Bowling Headquarters 3/27/69.4, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/25)
  - Hamlin Park 3/27/69.5, 1969 (Box-folder 2/26)
  - Westlake Park (Mall) 3/27/69.6, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Westlake Park (Mall) 3/27/69.6, 1969 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Westlake Park (Mall) 3/27/69.6, 1969 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Discovery Park 032769.7, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Discovery Park 032769.7, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Discovery Park 032769.7, 1969 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Discovery Park - Designer Interviews 032769.7, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Discovery Park - Designer Interviews 032769.7, 1969 (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Discovery Park - Designer Interviews 032769.7, 1969 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Central Waterfront Park 3/27/69.8, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Central Waterfront Park 3/27/69.8, 1973 (Box-folder 3/11)
  - Central Waterfront Park 3/27/69.8, 1972 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Central Waterfront Park 3/27/69.8, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - 28th Avenue Northeast - Paving 3/27/69.9, 1969 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - 27th Avenue Southwest, from Southwest Cambridge Street to Southwest Roxbury Street 3/27/69.10, 1969 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Fire Station 18 3/27/69.11, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Metro Pumping Stations (Belvoir and 30th Avenue Northeast) 4/10/69.3, 1969 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Street Furniture and Graphics Study 4/10/69.6, 1969 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Golf Drive Landscaping 4/10/69.7, 1969 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Stadium Parking Garages 4/10/69.8, 1969 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Edgewood Avenue Southwest 4/10/69.10, 1969 (Box-folder 4/9)
  - Northeast Northgate Way 4/10/69.11, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 4/10)
  - King County Stadium, 1969 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - King County Stadium, 1968 (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Aurora Median 4/24/69.5, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Triangles 4/24/69.6, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4/14)
  - Bay Freeway 4/24/69.10, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 4/15)
  - Camp Denny 5/14/69.1, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - Jackson Park Golf Course Club House 5/14/69.2, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/17)
  - Ross Playground Shelter House 5/14/69.3, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Roxhill Park 5/14/69.4, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - Arboretum Street Lighting 5/14/69.6, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - Alley in Rowe's Addition 5/14/69.7, 1969 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Fire Station 29 5/14/69.8, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Seattle Transit Shelter (Parkshore) 5/14/69.9, 1969 (Box-folder 4/23)
  - College Way North and Meridian Avenue North 051469.12 (Incorporating 071273.5), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 4/24)
  - College Way North and Meridian Avenue North 051469.12 (Incorporating 071273.5), 1975 (Box-folder 4/25)
  - College Way North and Meridian Avenue North 051469.12 (Incorporating 071273.5), 1975 (Box-folder 4/26)
  - College Way North and Meridian Avenue North 051469.12 (Incorporating 071273.5), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Seward Park Cultural Arts Center 6/11/69.1, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - South Fidalgo Street - Sidewalks 6/11/69.4, 1969 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Alley in Block 25, Brooklyn Addition 6/11/69.5, 1969 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Thorndyke Avenue Improvements 6/11/69.6, 1969 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Metro Sewer Regulators 6/11/69.7, 1969 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - Garfield Running Track (Shelter House) 6/11/69.8, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - Delridge Playfield Restroom Siting 6/11/69.10, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - Charles Street Shops 6/11/69.11, 1969 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Camp Long Security 6/11/69.12, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Roxbury A and B and Olson Place Street Improvements 6/11/69.13, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Yesler-Atlantic Pedestrian Walkway 7/9/69.2, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 5/12)
  - Meadowbrook Playfield Tennis Courts 7/9/69.4, 1969 (Box-folder 5/13)
  - Lincoln Park Tennis Courts 7/9/69.5, 1969 (Box-folder 5/14)
  - North Shore View Park 7/9/69.11, 1969 (Box-folder 5/15)
  - South Weller Street Improvement 7/9/69.15, 1969 (Box-folder 5/16)
  - Alley, Block 1, Kingsbury Heights Addition 7/9/69.16, 1969 (Box-folder 5/17)
  - Fuhrman Avenue East Sidewalk Improvement 7/9/69.17, 1969 (Box-folder 5/18)
  - 1st Avenue Northeast 7/9/69.18, 1969 (Box-folder 5/19)
  - Northwest 87th Street Paving 7/9/69.19, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 5/20)
  - Terry Avenue Paving 7/9/69.20, 1969 (Box-folder 5/21)
  - North Administrative Center 7/23/69.1, 1969 (Box-folder 5/22)
  - Color Presentation 7/23/69.2, 1969 (Box-folder 5/23)
  - East Pacific Street Pedestrian Overpass 8/6/69.3, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/24)
  - Georgetown Playfield Lighting 8/6/69.5, 1969 (Box-folder 5/25)
  - West Green Lake Bath House Theater 8/6/69.9, 1969 (Box-folder 5/26)
  - Magnolia Interceptor Project 8/6/69.11, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/27)
  - Charles Street - Motor Transportation Division Garage Building 8/6/69.13, 1969 (Box-folder 5/28)
  - Fire Station 19 8/6/69.14, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/29)
  - Fire Station 34 8/6/69.15, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 5/30)
  - Yesler Neighborhood Center 8/28/69.7, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 5/31)
  - Union Street Receiving Substation 8/28/69.11, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 5/32)
  - Elephant House 8/28/69.12, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/33)
  - Bar S Playground 8/28/69.13, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/34)
  - University Floral Hall 9/24/69.1, 1969 (Box-folder 5/35)
  - Street Tree Growing Contract 9/24/69.2, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/36)
  - Montlake Boulevard Street Widening 9/24/69.4, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/37)
  - South Oregon Street 9/24/69.5, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/38)
  - Volunteer Park Master Plan 9/24/69.13, 1969-1983 (Box-folder 5/39)
  - Seward Park Bike Trails 9/24/69.16, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/40)
  - Modification to Rainier Avenue Pumping Station (Metro) 10/8/69.2, 1969 (Box-folder 5/41)
  - Dexter Avenue Regulator Station (Metro) 10/8/69.3, 1969 (Box-folder 5/42)
  - Harrison Mini Park 10/8/69.4, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/43)
  - Bus Shelter/Williams Place 11/12/69.1, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 5/44)
  - Westlake Park 11/12/69.4, 1969-1980 (Box-folder 5/45)
  - Meridian Avenue Planting - Phase I 11/12/69.8, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 5/46)
  - Dearborne Street Planting 11/12/69.9, 1969 (Box-folder 5/47)
  - Westlake Park 11/12/69.10, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 5/48)
  - Westlake Park 11/12/69.10, 1980 (Box-folder 5/49)
  - Westlake Park 11/12/69.10, 1969 (Box-folder 5/50)
  - Alley in Block, Sanders Addition 11/12/69.12, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - South Myrtle Street 11/12/69.13, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - South Director Street 11/12/69.14, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - South Juneau Street 11/12/69.15, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - Lake Park Drive Light Poles 12/4/69.2, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Ingraham Swimming Pool 12/4/69.4, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Stone Avenue North 12/4/69.5, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - 50th Avenue South 12/18/69.1, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Alley Block and Craven Addition 12/18/69.2, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/9)
  - Corson Avenue South and South Kenyon Street 12/18/69.3, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/10)
  - Jefferson Park Recreation Center 12/18/69.4, 1969 (Box-folder 6/11)
  - Children's Zoo Theater 12/18/69.5, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 6/12)
  - Firehouse Park 12/18/69.7, 1969 (Box-folder 6/13)
  - Rainier Beach Swimming Pool 12/18/69.8, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 6/14)
  - Garfield Running Track Shelter 12/18/69.9, 1969 (Box-folder 6/15)
  - Ballard Pool 1/22/70.1, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 6/16)
  - Lighting Projects 1/22/70.6, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 6/17)
  - Matthew Beach Master Plan 1/22/70.7, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 6/18)
  - Mini-Parks 1/22/70.8, 1970-1982 (Box-folder 6/19)
  - Pedestrian Overcrossing 1/22/70.10, 1970 (Box-folder 6/20)
  - Fire Station 4 1/22/70.14, 1970 (Box-folder 6/21)
  - 38th Avenue South 1/22/70.15, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 6/22)
  - 15th Avenue South 1/22/70.16, 1970 (Box-folder 6/23)
  - Central Waterfront Study 1/22/70.17, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 6/24)
  - Blue Streak Parking Program 2/26/70.6, 1970 (Box-folder 6/25)
  - Williams Place Transit Shelter 2/26/70.9, 1970-1982 (Box-folder 6/26)
  - Alley Block 4, Denny's Addition 2/26/70.10, 1970 (Box-folder 6/27)
  - 44th Avenue Northeast 2/26/70.11, 1970 (Box-folder 6/28)
  - Appliance Service Headquarters - City Light 4/9/70.1, 1970 (Box-folder 6/29)
  - Charles Street Maintenance Shop Master Plan 4/9/70.2, 1969-1982 (Box-folder 6/30)
  - Camp Long Lighting 4/9/70.4, 1970 (Box-folder 6/31)
  - Woodlawn Avenue North 4/9/70.5, 1970 (Box-folder 6/32)
  - Alley Block 49 4/9/70.6, 1970 (Box-folder 6/33)
  - Maplewood Playfield (Formerly Beacon Hill Playfield) 4/9/70.8, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 6/34)
  - Graphic Study (Parks) 4/9/70.13, 1970 (Box-folder 6/35)
  - Gasworks Park (Myrtle Edwards / Lake Union Park) 040970.14, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 6/36)
  - Garfield Playfield Improvement Schematic Design 4/23/70.1, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 6/37)
  - North and South Shore View Point 4/23/70.2, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 6/38)
  - Aquarium 4/23/70.3, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 6/39)
  - Aquarium 4/23/70.3, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 6/40)
  - Aquarium 4/23/70.3, 1973 (Box-folder 6/41)
  - Aquarium 4/23/70.3, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Aquarium 4/23/70.3, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - 33rd Avenue East - Construction Drawings 4/23/70.7, 1970 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - 26th Avenue South - Construction Drawings 4/23/70.8, 1970 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Meridian Avenue South 4/23/70.9, 1970 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - North Acres Park Master Plan Schematic Design 5/7/70.1, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - 16th Avenue Southwest - Unit A, Design Development, Paving 5/7/70.4, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - Lake City Community Center Park - Selection of Designer 5/7/70.5, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Southwest Charleston Street 5/21/70.4, 1970 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - 36th Avenue Northeast 5/21/70.5, 1970 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - 8th Avenue Northeast 5/21/70.7, 1970 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - 30th Avenue Mini-Park 6/11/70.3, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/12)
  - 26th Avenue Mini-Park 6/11/70.4, 1970 (Box-folder 7/13)
  - Spring Street Mini-Park 6/11/70.5, 1970 (Box-folder 7/14)
  - Elliott Bay Grain Terminal 6/11/70.7, 1970 (Box-folder 7/15)
  - East Alder Street Improvement 6/11/70.8, 1970 (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Olson Place Southwest 6/11/70.9, 1970 (Box-folder 7/17)
  - Central Freeway Park East Plaza Garage 6/25/70.6, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Central Freeway Park East Plaza Garage 6/25/70.6, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - Southwest Trenton Street 6/25/70.7, 1970 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - 59th Avenue South 6/25/70.8, 1970 (Box-folder 7/21)
  - Elliott Avenue West 6/25/70.9, 1970 (Box-folder 7/22)
  - 8th Avenue Northwest 6/25/70.10, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 7/23)
  - Wall of Respect 7/23/70.3, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 7/24)
  - Meadowbrook Playfield - Shelter House 7/23/70.9, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 7/25)
  - Transit Sign - Blue Streak 7/23/70.11, 1970 (Box-folder 7/26)
  - Magnolia Triangle 7/23/70.12, 1970 (Box-folder 7/27)
  - Woodland Park - Children's Zoo Expansion 7/23/70.13, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 7/28)
  - North 133rd Street 7/23/70.15, 1970 (Box-folder 7/29)
  - Greenwood Avenue North 7/23/70.16, 1970 (Box-folder 7/30)
  - Fire Station 36 8/13/70.8, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 7/31)
  - Fire Station 33 8/13/70.10, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/32)
  - California Avenue Southwest Stairway 8/13/70.12, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/33)
  - 30th Avenue Northeast Sidewalk 8/13/70.13, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/34)
  - 6th Avenue and Vine Street Triangle 8/13/70.14, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/35)
  - Madrona Bathhouse 9/10/70.3, 1970-1982 (Box-folder 7/36)
  - Sacajawea Playground 9/10/70.5, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/37)
  - Perkins Lane Toe Wall 9/10/70.10, 1970-1981 (Box-folder 7/38)
  - Barton Place 9/10/70.14, 1970 (Box-folder 7/39)
  - North 143rd Street 9/10/70.15, 1970 (Box-folder 7/40)
  - West Seattle Golf Course 9/10/70.16, 1970 (Box-folder 7/41)
  - Rainier Avenue / Empire Way Pedestrian Overpass 9/24/70.4, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 7/42)
  - Charles Street Complex - Personnel Building 9/24/70.5, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/43)
  - Alley in Block 8 Dumar Addition 9/24/70.6, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/44)
  - Alaska Parkway Extension 10/8/70.1, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 7/45)
  - 30th Avenue Northwest - Low Impact Development 10/8/70.2, 1970 (Box-folder 7/46)
  - Herzl Synagogue 10/22/70.10, 1970 (Box-folder 7/47)
  - Pioneer Square / Occidental Park 10/22/70.14, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 7/48)
  - 25th Avenue South - Low Impact Development 11/12/70.5, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 7/49)
  - 35th Avenue Southwest - Street Improvement 11/12/70.6, 1970 (Box-folder 7/50)
  - 6th Avenue Lighting 11/12/70.7, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/51)
  - Mount Baker Park 12/3/70.3, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 7/52)
  - Loyal Heights 12/3/70.5, 1970-1981 (Box-folder 7/53)
  - Taylor Mill Sanitary Sewer System - Sites at 72nd Avenue South and South Perry Street 12/3/70.8, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 7/54)
  - Street Tree Planting Project 1/14/71.1, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Seattle Central Community College 1/14/71.2, 1970 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Alley Block 34 - Seaview Addition 1/14/71.3, 1971 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Northeast 86th Street Permit Number L0912 1/14/71.4, 1971 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Northeast Pacific Street Relocation 1/28/71.1, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Pioneer Square Neighborhood Health Center 1/28/71.3, 1971 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Northeast 96th Street (Low Impact Development) 1/28/71.6, 1971 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - West Armour Street 1/28/71.8, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - North and Northeast 92nd Street Widening 2/11/71.6, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Loyal Heights - Parking 2/11/71.8, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Northgate Way Sidewalks 2/25/71.1, 1971 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Bus Stop Shelters - Yesler Avenue and 15th Avenue 2/25/71.2, 1971 (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Street Lighting Program - Arterial 1970 2/25/71.3, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Woodland Park Tennis Courts 2/25/71.5, 1971 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - South Ferdinand Street 3/11/71.1, 1971 (Box-folder 8/15)
  - South Pearl Street 3/11/71.2, 1971 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - 17th Avenue South 3/11/71.3, 1971 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Odessa Brown Neighborhood Health Facility 3/11/71.4, 1971 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Red Barn Ranch Briefing 3/11/71.5, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Fire Station 26 3/11/71.6, 1971 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Herzel Neighborhood Health Station 3/25/71.1, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Empire Way South - Sidewalks 3/25/71.4, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Aurora-Denny Way Street Improvement 3/25/71.5, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Ballard Recreation Center Athletic Field Lighting 3/25/71.7, 1971 (Box-folder 8/24)
  - International District Mini-Park 4/8/71.4, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Meadowbrook Swimming Pool 4/8/71.5, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 8/26)
  - Fire Apparatus Maintenance Shop 4/8/71.6, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 8/27)
  - Bus Stop Shelter - 2nd and Yesler and 24th and East Union 4/8/71.7, 1971 (Box-folder 8/28)
  - Empire Way South 4/8/71.8, 1971 (Box-folder 8/29)
  - Delridge Way Southwest / Southwest Barton Street / 18th Avenue Southwest Triangle 4/22/71.2, 1971 (Box-folder 8/30)
  - 23rd Avenue underground Project 4/22/71.5, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 8/31)
  - 33rd Avenue East / East Spring Street 5/6/71.1, 1971 (Box-folder 8/32)
  - 24th Avenue West 5/6/71.2, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/33)
  - Southwest Genesee Street 5/6/71.3, 1971 (Box-folder 8/34)
  - 35th Avenue South and Related Streets 5/6/71.4, 1971 (Box-folder 8/35)
  - Water Quality Building Additions 5/6/71.9, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 8/36)
  - Pinehurst Playground 5/27/71.4, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 8/37)
  - Alley Paving in Block 22, South Park Addition 5/27/71.8, 1971 (Box-folder 8/38)
  - Alley Paving, Blocks 1 and 2, Prosser Addition 5/27/71.9, 1971 (Box-folder 8/39)
  - Alley Paving in Baird's Tract F (Model Cities) 5/27/71.10, 1971 (Box-folder 8/40)
  - Alley Paving in Block 4, West Hill 5/27/71.11, 1971 (Box-folder 8/41)
  - West Emerson Street Sidewalk 5/27/71.12, 1971 (Box-folder 8/42)
  - Alley Paving in Block 11 of Hillman's Addition 5/27/71.13, 1971 (Box-folder 8/43)
  - South Walker Street Sidewalks 5/27/71.14, 1971 (Box-folder 8/44)
  - Northern Life Building Skybridge 5/27/71.15, 1971 (Box-folder 8/45)
  - Mercer Street Sidewalk Paving 6/10/71.3, 1971 (Box-folder 8/46)
  - 5th Avenue Street Tree Plantings 6/23/71.6, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/47)
  - South Main Street and Other Street Improvements in Yesler-Atlantic Project, 1971 (Box-folder 8/48)
  - Empire Way South - Widening and Cutback 6/24/71.5, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 8/49)
  - Northeast 125th Street (Tree Plantings and Triangles) 7/15/71.6, 1971 (Box-folder 8/50)
  - Tenth Avenue East - Widening, etc. 7/15/71.9, 1973 (Box-folder 8/51)
  - Alley in Block 48 Plat of Town of Seattle 7/15/71.11, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 8/52)
  - Delridge / Barton and Fauntleroy Genesee - Triangle Project 7/29/71.1, 1971 (Box-folder 8/53)
  - Bench Advertising 8/26/71.1, 1971 (Box-folder 8/54)
  - Pedestrian Underpass at 21st Avenue South and South Jackson Street 8/26/71.2, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/55)
  - 37th Avenue Park 8/26/71.6, 1971 (Box-folder 8/56)
  - Children's Play Area Hiawatha Playfield 8/26/71.8, 1971 (Box-folder 8/57)